<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Jeffrey Cyphers Wright</title>
    <link>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Jeffrey Cyphers Wright</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Lyre</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/blue-lyre/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/blue-lyre/</guid>
      <description>Blue Lyre 2018
Dos Madres Press
New York, NY
Jeffrey Cyphers Wright is a leading voice of New Romanticism in the American Underground. His 15th book is a collection of stand-alone poems that combine to form a powerful portrait of a citizen, lover, family member, and seasoned artist. Blue Lyre will pull your leg and your heartstrings.
 &amp;hellip;comments about relationships, bar-hopping, and the creative process, are all tied, sometimes transparently, sometimes obscurely, to an ecological perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fake Lies</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/fake-lies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/fake-lies/</guid>
      <description>Fake Lies, © 2018 by Jeffrey Cyphers Wright is Fell Swoop 159.
 Fell Swoop in New Orleans just published “Fake Lies”. Those poems will end up in a collection called Dopple Gängster which is the new stuff I’m working on.
Although the poems are stand alone, they call and echo each other. They’re about a central figure moving through the landscape, who tries to maintain an upbeat spirituality and the struggle to share that sensation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio Poems</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/radio-poems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 08:40:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/radio-poems/</guid>
      <description>Radio Poems 2017
The Operating System
New York, NY
&amp;ldquo;You should always write with the radio on.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Ted Berrigan
 Not since Cocteau’s film, Orpheus, has a writer tapped into the poetic unconscious of the radio with such witty and marvelous results. Jeffrey Cyphers Wright’s &amp;lsquo;Radio&amp;rsquo; plays nonstop hit poems with an energizing staccato rhythm that brings the &amp;ldquo;divine monkey business&amp;rdquo; that is New York and its many underground scenes back to life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Employment of the Apes</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/employment-of-the-apes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 19:20:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/employment-of-the-apes/</guid>
      <description>This hybrid text &amp;ldquo;verse-journal&amp;rdquo; humorously and lovingly keeps track of Bohemian life in the East Village in an era of punk and political regression. With artwork by Alice Notley, Andrei Codrescu, Lisa Eshelman, Jim Moser and the author.
  Employment of the Apes 1981
Chronic Editions
ISBN:093887800X
Dennis Cooper wrote in Beyond Baroque:
 Wright&amp;rsquo;s talent appears bright&amp;hellip; as well as attractive in the categories of feeling, inspiration and temperament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Triple Crown</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/triple-crown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 12:33:11 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/triple-crown/</guid>
      <description>cover art by Renee Ricard and JCW
Triple Crown 2013
Three Crowns of Sonnets
by Jeffrey Cyphers Wright
Spuyten Duyvil
ISBN:978-1-881471-23-3
From the Urban Graffiti Review:
 Jeff Wright&amp;rsquo;s lyrical liberties propel the traditional sonnet on a worldwide dash. Every poem is &amp;ldquo;Made in&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; somewhere &amp;ndash;beginning with China. In the second poem, &amp;ldquo;Made in Hong Kong,&amp;rdquo; the initial entreaty beckons with musical sophistication: anagrammatic words coupled in a double-beat rhyme scheme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Party Everywhere</title>
      <link>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/party-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 10:10:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeffreycypherswright.com/books/party-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>Party Everywhere 2014
Xanadu Press
ISBN:0-9760793-9-9
 This poem is a manifesto for the nascient &amp;lsquo;eventworks&amp;rsquo; movement that stresses collaboration, community, and cause-based art. Welcome to the new world ardor. &amp;ndash;Michael Andre
 A poet&amp;rsquo;s guide to social engagement
  Write your own &amp;ldquo;ticket&amp;rdquo;
Sing here
Remember, you are a can,
not a can not
   Centerfold from Party Everywhere
Wright created this book-length poem, photo-collage, photo-assemblage, thanks to a summer residency at eMediaLoft in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>